Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - O
        - O2 - It's time, 1994; SR-21785; O2 (Box 377)
          Catalog # CRO-2-001; A-side Matrix # CRO-2-001-A
          Cliche Records
          Fort Worth, Texas
        - Oak - Snakes in the grass, 2005; SR-21786; Oak (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21787; SR-21788. Different discs.
          Catalog # WAX-0105; A-side Matrix # 62054E1/A
          Wax On
          United Kingdom
        - (Unlabeled test pressing), SR-21787 (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21786; SR-21788. Different discs. Test Pressing
          Catalog # PRCD-90; A-side Matrix # PRCD-90-A
          Dunmore, Pennsylvania
        - Vigorito, Danilo - Pumpin, 2004; SR-21788; Vigorito, Danilo (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21786; SR-21787. Different discs.
          Catalog # ORION 006; A-side Matrix # ORION 006 A
          Orion Muzik
          Italy
        - Oaktown's 3-5-7 and M.C. Hammer - Juicy gotchy krazy, 1989; SR-21789; Oaktown's 3-5-7; M.C. Hammer (Box 377)
          Catalog # V-15510; A-side Matrix # V-1-15510-2
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Oas, Holly - He's a rebel, 1984; SR-21790; Oas, Holly (Box 377)
          Catalog # DD-105; A-side Matrix # DD-105-A
          D&D Records
        - Chief Commander Ebenezer Obey and his Inter-Reformers Band - Eyi yato, 1981; SR-21791; Chief Commander Ebenezer Obey and his Inter-Reformers Band (Box 377)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # OTI(LP)508; A-side Matrix # OTILP 508A
          Oti
          London, United Kingdom
        - Obi 1 and Absolute Youngins Band - The D.C. joint, 2001; SR-21792; Obi 1; Absolute Youngins Band (Box 377)
          Promo
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 7364-C JOINT-1 (A) S-48321
          House of Ra Inner-Attainment
          United States
        - Obi 1 and Absolute Youngins Band - The D.C. joint, 2001; SR-21793; Obi 1; Absolute Youngins Band (Box 377)
        - Obi 1 and Absolute Youngins Band - The D.C. joint, 2001; SR-21794; Obi 1; Absolute Youngins Band (Box 377)
        - Obie Trice, 2003; SR-21795; Busta Rhymes; Dr. Dre; Eminem (Box 377)
          Catalog # INTR-11040-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-11040-1 A
          Interscope Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - O'Bryan - Driving force, 1986; SR-21796; O'Bryan (Box 377)
          Catalog # V-15275; A-side Matrix # V-1-15275-100499 & 100499-A
        - O'Bryan - Breakin' together, 1984; SR-21797; O'Bryan (Box 377)
          Catalog # V-8605; A-side Matrix # V-8605-99286-B
        - O'Bryan - Lovelite, 1984; SR-21798; O'Bryan (Box 377)
          Catalog # V-8583; A-side Matrix # V-8583-99251-B
        - O'Bryan - The gigolo, 1981; SR-21799; O'Bryan (Box 377)
          Catalog # SPRO-9731; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9731
        - Ocasek, Ric - Prove; Connect to me, 1982; SR-21800; Ocasek, Ric (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21801. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-2002; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2002-SH1
          Geffen Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - Ocasek, Ric - Prove; Connect to me, 1982; SR-21801; Ocasek, Ric (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21800. 2 copies. Promo
        - Ocasek, Ric - Beatitude, 1982; SR-21802; Ocasek, Ric (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21803. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GHS 2022; A-side Matrix # GHS-1-2022-A-SR2
        - Ocasek, Ric - Beatitude, 1982; SR-21803; Ocasek, Ric (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21802. 2 copies.
        - Ocasek, Ric - Jimmy Jimmy, 1983; SR-21804; Ocasek, Ric (Box 377)
          Catalog # 0-20114; A-side Matrix # 0-20114-A-SH1
        - Ocean, Billy - Inner feelings, 1982; SR-21805; Ocean, Billy (Box 377)
          Catalog # EPC CX 85568; A-side Matrix # 01-85568-2A-1
          Epic
          New York, New York
        - Ocean, Billy - Stay the night, 1981; SR-21806; Ocean, Billy (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21807. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # 48-02049; A-side Matrix # XSS 168554-1A
        - Ocean, Billy - Stay the night, 1981; SR-21807; Ocean, Billy (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21806. Different discs.
          Catalog # 48-02049; A-side Matrix # XSS 168554-1D
        - Oceania - Kotahitanga (The Eric Kupper remixes), 2000; SR-21808; Oceania (Box 377)
          No label
          Catalog # UCGR-00009-1; A-side Matrix # UCGR-00009-1A
          Germany
        - Oceanic - Insanity, 1991; SR-21809; Oceanic (Box 377)
          Catalog # DMD 1740; A-side Matrix # ST DM-61148-61149-2
          EastWest Records America
        - O.C.M. - Watch how you slang, 1994; SR-21810; O.C.M. (Box 377)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7340; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7340-A-SR1
          Qwest Records
          Burbank, California
        - O.C.M. - Watch how you slang, 1994; SR-21811; O.C.M. (Box 377)
          Catalog # 0-41682-A; A-side Matrix # 0 41682 A SR1
        - O'Connor, Sinead and MC Lyte - I want your (hands on me), 1988; SR-21812; O'Connor, Sinead; MC Lyte (Box 377)
          Catalog # 609 958; A-side Matrix # DM609958 A-1/4-88
          Ensign
        - Octavia - 2 the limit, 1986; SR-21813; Octavia (Box 377)
          Catalog # PW 415; A-side Matrix # PW-415-A
          Pow Wow Records
        - O.C.U. - I'm all that (you're my everything), 1991; SR-21814; O.C.U. (Box 377)
          Catalog # 10121; A-side Matrix # OCU-10121-A-GIA
          Kapone Records & Filmworks
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Odd Company - Swing in trance, 1992; SR-21815; Odd Company (Box 377)
          Catalog # LUK 004; A-side Matrix # LUK 004-A
          Logic Records UK
        - Odeed and Bionic - The demons; The bullet, 2002; SR-21816; Odeed; Bionic (Box 377)
          Test Pressing
          Catalog # MG 83001-1; A-side Matrix # MG 83001-1 A
          Moonshine Music
        - O'dell and Porsha - Nothing stays the same, 1999; SR-21817; O'dell; Porsha (Box 377)
          Catalog # SPRO 81181; A-side Matrix # 08724-81181-17-A
          No Limit Records
          New Orleans, Louisiana
        - Odette - Love walked (out of my life), 1988; SR-21818; Odette (Box 377)
          Catalog # DT 4001; A-side Matrix # DT-4001 A
          Disc-Tinct
        - Odyssey - Lucky star, 1978; SR-21819; Odyssey (Box 377)
          Catalog # JD-11445; A-side Matrix # PD 11445-A
          RCA Victor
        - Odyssey - The greatest hits (disc one), 1987; SR-21820; Odyssey (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21821. Double album.
          Catalog # SMR 735; A-side Matrix # DM B-9067 A-1/9-87
          Stylus Music
        - Odyssey - The greatest hits (disc two), 1987; SR-21821; Odyssey (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21820. Double album.
          Catalog # SMR 735; A-side Matrix # DM B-9068 A-1/9-87
        - Odyssey - Single again; What time does the balloon go up; Pride, 1978; SR-21822; Odyssey (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21823. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # JD-11400; A-side Matrix # PD-11400-A
        - Odyssey - Lucky star, 1978; SR-21823; Odyssey (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21822. Different discs. Promo
        - Odyssey - Inside out, 1982; SR-21824; Odyssey (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21825. Different discs. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # JT-13218; A-side Matrix # PD 13218-A-1
          RCA
        - Odyssey - Happy together, 1982; SR-21825; Odyssey (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21824. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFL1-4240; A-side Matrix # AFL1 4240 A-1
        - Odyssey - Odyssey, 1977; SR-21826; Odyssey (Box 377)
          Catalog # APL1-2204; A-side Matrix # APL-1-2204-A-16
        - Odyssey - Hang together, 1980; SR-21827; Odyssey (Box 377)
          Catalog # AFL1-3526; A-side Matrix # AFL-1-3526-A
        - Off Da Hook - Off da hook, 1996; SR-21828; Off Da Hook; Dirty Dave; Peeba (Box 377)
          Catalog # RDAB-64606-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-64604-1-A1
          Loud Records
        - Off Da Hook - Off da hook, 1996; SR-21829; Off Da Hook; Dirty Dave; Peeba (Box 377)
        - Off Da Hook - Off da hizzie, 1996; SR-21830; Off Da Hook (Box 377)
          Catalog # RDAA-64668-1; A-side Matrix # RDAA-64668-1 A1
        - Off Limits - Round and round, 1990; SR-21831; Off Limits (Box 377)
          Catalog # DW 1914; A-side Matrix # DW 1914-A
          Dance and Waves
          Bologna, Italy
        - Off Shore - I can't take the power, 1990; SR-21832; Off Shore (Box 377)
          Catalog # 45 73751; A-side Matrix # XSS 73751A-1A
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - Bugging out, 1985; SR-21833; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz (Box 377)
          Catalog # WB 77303; A-side Matrix # WB-77304-A
          Web Records
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - Bounce to the ounce, 1999; SR-21834; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz; Havoc (Box 377)
          Catalog # SPRO 81203; A-side Matrix # 53495-11-A-1
          Priority Records
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - Bounce to the ounce, 1999; SR-21835; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz; Havoc (Box 377)
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - Hurricane Starang, 1997; SR-21836; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz (Box 377)
          Catalog # SPRO 30126; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30126-A
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - No fear, 1996; SR-21837; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz (Box 377)
          Catalog # SPRO 30081; A-side Matrix # PVL-53243-A
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - Da storm (disc one), 1996; SR-21838; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21839. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50577; A-side Matrix # P1-50577-A
        - O.G.C./Originoo Gunn Clappaz - Da storm (disc two), 1996; SR-21839; O.G.C.; Originoo Gunn Clappaz; Bad Vybes; M.S.; Representativz; Sadat X; Black, Sean (Box 377)
          In same jacket as # SR-21838. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50577; A-side Matrix # P1-50577-C
        - Ohio Express - The best of Ohio Express, 1970; SR-21840; Ohio Express (Box 378)
          Catalog # BDS 5058; A-side Matrix # BS 5058-A
          Buddha Records
        - Ohio Players - Ouch!, 1981; SR-21841; Ohio Players (Box 378)
          Catalog # NB1-33247; A-side Matrix # NB1-AL-33247
          The Boardwalk Entertainment Co.
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Ohio Players - Back, 1988; SR-21842; Ohio Players (Box 378)
          Catalog # TRK-58810-1; A-side Matrix # TRK-58810-1-A
          Track Record Company
          Seattle, Washington
        - Ohio Players - Back, 1988; SR-21843; Ohio Players (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21844. 2 copies.
        - Ohio Players - Back, 1988; SR-21844; Ohio Players (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21843. 2 copies.
        - Ohio Players - Skin tight, 1974; SR-21845; Ohio Players (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21846. Different discs.
          Catalog # 6338 497; A-side Matrix # 6338 497 1
          Mercury
        - Ohio Players - Skin tight, 1974; SR-21846; Ohio Players (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21845. Different discs.
          Catalog # SRM-1-705; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-705 A-CT12
        - Ohm - Heady volts sensation EP, 1990; SR-21847; Ohm (Box 378)
          Catalog # BUST 001; A-side Matrix # BUST-001 A
          Buster Gutt Records
        - Ohm - Heady volts sensation EP, 1990; SR-21848; Ohm (Box 378)
        - Oingo Boingo - Private life; Nothing to fear (but fear itself), 1982; SR-21849; Oingo Boingo (Box 378)
          Catalog # SP-17203; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-017203-A-(RE-1)
          A&M Records
        - O'Jays - Family reunion, 1975; SR-21850; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # PZ 33807; A-side Matrix # AL-33807-1H
          Philadelphia International Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - O'Jays - Lovin' you, 1987; SR-21851; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # 12 PIR 6; A-side Matrix # 12 PIR 6 A-1-1-1-1
        - O'Jays - So full of love, 1978; SR-21852; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # JZ 35355; A-side Matrix # AL-35355-1C
        - O'Jays - Back stabbers, 1972; SR-21853; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # KZ 31712; A-side Matrix # AL-31712
        - O'Jays - Put our heads together, 1983; SR-21854; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04073; A-side Matrix # AA-4Z9-04073-3
        - O'Jays - Live in London, 1974; SR-21855; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # KZ 32953; A-side Matrix # AL-32953-1A
        - O'Jays - Pay the bills, 1997; SR-21856; O'Jays (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21857. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # VP37226-1; A-side Matrix # VP-37226-1-A
          Volcano Entertainment, L.L.C.
        - O'Jays - Pay the bills, 1997; SR-21857; O'Jays (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21856. 2 copies. Promo
        - O'Jays - Lovin' you; Don't let the dream get away, 1987; SR-21858; O'Jays (Box 378)
          Catalog # SPRO-79129; A-side Matrix # SPRO-79129-Z1
        - Oktober - NYC; Sounds like drama, 2004; SR-21859; Oktober (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21860. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FR024-1; A-side Matrix # FR024A
          Freshchest
        - Oktober - NYC; Sounds like drama, 2004; SR-21860; Oktober (Box 378)
          In same jacket as # SR-21859. 2 copies.
        - Ol' Dirty Bastard - Brooklyn zoo, 1995; SR-21861; Ol' Dirty Bastard (Box 378)
          Catalog # ED 5724; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5724 A2
          Elektra
        - Ol' Dirty Bastard - Got your money, 2000; SR-21862; Ol' Dirty Bastard; Kelis (Box 378)
          Catalog # E7077T; A-side Matrix # E7077T A1
        - Ol' Dirty Bastard - Intoxicated, 2005; SR-21863; ODB; Ol' Dirty Bastard; Gray, Macy; Method Man; Raekwon (Box 378)
          Catalog # DEFR 16275-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16275-1-A-RE1
          Damon Dash Music Group
        - Ol' Dirty Bastard - ODB, don't go breaking my heart, 2005; SR-21864; ODB; Ol' Dirty Bastard; Gray, Macy (Box 378)
          Catalog # DEFR 16347-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR16347-1 A
        - Ol' Dirty Bastard - Recognize, 1999; SR-21865; Ol' Dirty Bastard (Box 378)
          Catalog # ED-6193; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6193 A-2
        - Ol' Skool - Set you free, 1997; SR-21866; Ol' Skool (Box 378)
          Catalog # U12-56145; A-side Matrix # U12-56145A-RE1
          Universal Records
        - Ol' Skool - Am I dreaming, 1997; SR-21867; Ol' Skool; Xscape (Box 378)
          Catalog # U8P-1239; A-side Matrix # U8P-1239 A
        - Ol' Skool - Ol Skool, 1997; SR-21868; Ol' Skool; Sweat, Keith; Xscape (Box 378)
          Catalog # U-53104; A-side Matrix # U-53104-A
        - Ol' Skool - Only one, 1999; SR-21869; Ol' Skool; Sweat, Keith (Box 378)
          Catalog # U8P 1524; A-side Matrix # U8P-1524A
        - Olatunji, Babatunde - Dance to the beat of my drum, 1986; SR-21870; Olatunji, Babatunde (Box 378)
          Catalog # BLU 706; A-side Matrix # BLU 706 A
          Blue Heron Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Olatunji, Babatunde - Dance to the beat of my drum, 1986; SR-21871; Olatunji, Babatunde (Box 378)
        - Oldfield, Mike - Family man; Five miles out, 1982; SR-21872; Oldfield, Mike (Box 378)
          Catalog # AS 1424; A-side Matrix # XSM170065-1B
        - Oliver, Bonnie - Come inside my love, 1979; SR-21873; Oliver, Bonnie (Box 378)
          Catalog # DISCO 3017; A-side Matrix # ZCL-8250-12
          Lejoint
        - Oliver, Valerie - (GTM) get the money, 1983; SR-21874; Oliver, Valerie (Box 378)
          Catalog # CY-905; A-side Matrix # CY-905-A
          Cyclops Records
        - Olivia - Cloud 9, 2005; SR-21875; Olivia; 50 Cent (Box 378)
          Catalog # CLOUD10; A-side Matrix # CLOUD9-A
          G Unit
        - Olodum - The best of Olodum, 1992; SR-21876; Olodum; Jimmy Cliff (Box 378)
          Catalog # 1-07-405-499; A-side Matrix # 107 405 499 A
          Continental
          Sao Paulo, Brazil
        - Olodum - Filhos do sol, 1994; SR-21877; Olodum (Box 378)
          Catalog # 998253-1; A-side Matrix # 998253-1-A
        - Olori Rock - Ruff-n-tuff; Don't test me, 1994; SR-21878; Olori Rock (Box 378)
          Catalog # LR 331; A-side Matrix # LR-331 THIS RIDE
          LonGevity Records
          Columbia, Maryland
        - Olympic Runners - Get it while you can, 1978; SR-21879; Olympic Runners (Box 378)
          Catalog # RUN 012; A-side Matrix # OLMP/RUNNERS A1
          Polydor
        - Omar - There's nothing like this, 1990; SR-21880; Omar (Box 378)
          Catalog # KDLP 2; A-side Matrix # KDLP-2-A
          Kongo Dance
        - Omar - There's nothing like this (Trackmasters remix), 1995; SR-21881; Omar (Box 378)
          Catalog # RDAB-64432-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64432-1-A1
          Groovetown
        - Omar, Don - Reggaeton Latino, 2005; SR-21882; Omar, Don; Cheka; LDA (Box 378)
          Catalog # UBO-1063-0P; A-side Matrix # UBO-1063-0P A
          Urban Box Office
        - Omarr, Dwayne - Holy rock, 1985; SR-21883; Omarr, Dwayne (Box 378)
          Catalog # CR 10100; A-side Matrix # CR-10100-AS
          Critique
          Reading, Massachusetts
        - Omarr, Dwayne - This party's jam packed, 1982; SR-21884; Omarr, Dwayne (Box 378)
          Catalog # SUD-132; A-side Matrix # SUD-132A
          Survivor Records
          Coral Gables, Florida
        - Omega Defcon II - Deathnation, 1986; SR-21885; Omega Defcon II (Box 378)
          Catalog # TR-520804; A-side Matrix # TR-520804-A
          Alpha Omega Records
          Westport, Connecticut
        - Omni - All for the one, 1982; SR-21886; Omni (Box 378)
          Catalog # FRD-82-2; A-side Matrix # FRD-82-2-A
          Fountain Records
        - Omniscence, 1996; SR-21887; Sadat X (Box 378)
          Catalog # ED 6009; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6009-A-2
        - Omniscence - Amazin, 1995; SR-21888; Omniscence (Box 378)
          Catalog # ED 5785; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5785-A1
        - Omniverse - Never get enough, 1990; SR-21889; Omniverse (Box 378)
          Catalog # ANT 002; A-side Matrix # ANT 002 A
          Antima Records
        - One Be Lo - Sleepwalking; Unparalleled, 2005; SR-21890; One Be Lo; Ka Di; Magestik Legend (Box 378)
          Catalog # FB2521; A-side Matrix # FB2521-A
          Fat Beats
          Brooklyn, New York
        - One Nation Crew, 2000; SR-21891; Franklin, Kirk (Box 378)
          Catalog # INTR-10025-1; A-side Matrix # INTR 10025-1 A
          B-Rite Music
          Inglewood, California
        - One Pham - One life one pham, 1994; SR-21892; One Pham (Box 378)
          Catalog # FASHO-001; A-side Matrix # FASHO-001-A-RE
          Fa' Sho' Records
        - One-Two-Three - Runaway, 1983; SR-21893; One-Two-Three (Box 379)
          Catalog # PRL D 655; A-side Matrix # PRLD-655-AS
          Prelude Records
        - One Way - Wild night, 1982; SR-21894; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # MCA-5369; A-side Matrix # MCA-3195-W1
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California